Guide to the Rice University Art Gallery records, 1971-2017 UA 066
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VI: Exhibition print materials and curatorial files, 2010-2015
  - D-17, Sarah Oppenheimer, Sept. 16-Dec. 5, 2010: Events (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - D-17, Sarah Oppenheimer, Sept. 16-Dec. 5, 2010: Press release (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - D-17, Sarah Oppenheimer, Sept. 16-Dec. 5, 2010: Press received (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - D-17, Sarah Oppenheimer, Sept. 16-Dec. 5, 2010: Words & Art event notebook (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Northwest Corner, Southeast Light, Mary Temple, Feb. 3 - May 25, 2011: Installation (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Northwest Corner, Southeast Light, Mary Temple, Feb. 3 - May 25, 2011: Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Northwest Corner, Southeast Light, Mary Temple, Feb. 3 - May 25, 2011: Research (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Northwest Corner, Southeast Light, Mary Temple, Feb. 3 - May 25, 2011: Graphics (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Northwest Corner, Southeast Light, Mary Temple, Feb. 3 - May 25, 2011: Events (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Northwest Corner, Southeast Light, Mary Temple, Feb. 3 - May 25, 2011: Press release (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Northwest Corner, Southeast Light, Mary Temple, Feb. 3 - May 25, 2011: Press received (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Northwest Corner, Southeast Light, Mary Temple, Feb. 3 - May 25, 2011: Travel (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Salon of Beauty, Ana Serrano, Sept. 29 - Dec. 11, 2011: Graphics and paint colors (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Salon of Beauty, Ana Serrano, Sept. 29 - Dec. 11, 2011: Words and Art event notebook (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Joel Shapiro: New Installation: research and graphics (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Joel Shapiro: New Installation: Words and Art event notebook (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Frances Leland watercolors: Rice University Centennial exhibit at Cohen House, 2012-10 (Box 41, Folder 25a)
  - Reverse of Volume RG, Yasuaki Onishi, April 13 - June 24, 2012: graphics (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Gaia: New Installation, Sept. - Dec., 2013: Pre-install panel, Text panel (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Gaia: New Installation, Sept. - Dec., 2013: Graphics (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Gaia: New Installation, Sept. - Dec., 2013: Installation (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Gaia: New Installation, Sept. - Dec., 2013: Research (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Gaia: New Installation, Sept. - Dec., 2013: Press release (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Gaia: New Installation, Sept. - Dec., 2013: Press received (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Gaia: New Installation, Sept. - Dec., 2013: Travel (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Gaia: New Installation, 2013: Words and Art event notebook (Box 41, Folder 33a)
  - Wheel of Everyday Life, Gunilla Klingberg, Jan. 31 - March 17, 2013: Installation (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Wheel of Everyday Life, Gunilla Klingberg, Jan. 31 - March 17, 2013: Research (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Wheel of Everyday Life, Gunilla Klingberg, Jan. 31 - March 17, 2013: Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Wheel of Everyday Life, Gunilla Klingberg, Jan. 31 - March 17, 2013: Graphics (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Wheel of Everyday Life, Gunilla Klingberg, Jan. 31 - March 17, 2013: Events (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Wheel of Everyday Life, Gunilla Klingberg, Jan. 31 - March 17, 2013: Press release (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Wheel of Everyday Life, Gunilla Klingberg, Jan. 31 - March 17, 2013: Press received (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Wheel of Everyday Life, Gunilla Klingberg, Jan. 31 - March 17, 2013: Video space (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Wheel of Everyday Life, Gunilla Klingberg, Jan. 31 - March 17, 2013: Words and Art event notebook (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - Wheel of Everyday Life, Gunilla Klingberg, Jan. 31 - March 17, 2013: Catalogue text (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Unwoven Light, Soo Sunny Park, July-August, 2013: Installation (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - Unwoven Light, Soo Sunny Park, July-August, 2013: Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - Unwoven Light, Soo Sunny Park, July-August, 2013: Research (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - Unwoven Light, Soo Sunny Park, July-August, 2013: Press release (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - Unwoven Light, Soo Sunny Park, July-August, 2013: Press received (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - Unwoven Light, Soo Sunny Park, July-August, 2013: Graphics (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - Unwoven Light, Soo Sunny Park, July-August, 2013: Events (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - Unwoven Light, Soo Sunny Park, July-August, 2013: Travel (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - Unwoven Light, Soo Sunny Park, July-August, 2013: Video space - Roman Signer (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - Unwoven Light, Soo Sunny Park, July-August, 2013: Words and Art event notebook (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - Unbounded, Ben Butler, June 4 - August 28, 2015: Graphics and correspondence (Box 41, Folder 54)
  - Shotgun, Rice School of Architecture students, Jan. 30 - March 15, 2015 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Intersections, Anila Quayyum Ahga, Sept. 24 - Dec. 6, 2015 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - El Ultimo Grito: Garden Object, March 2014: installation (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - El Ultimo Grito: Garden Object, March 2014: Research (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - El Ultimo Grito: Garden Object, March 2014: Graphics (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - El Ultimo Grito: Garden Object, March 2014: Events (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - El Ultimo Grito: Garden Object, March 2014: Press release (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - El Ultimo Grito: Garden Object, March 2014: Press received (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - El Ultimo Grito: Garden Object, March 2014: Video space / Sub-Dogma 13 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - El Ultimo Grito: Garden Object, March 2014: Travel (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - El Ultimo Grito: Garden Object, March 2014: Words and Art event notebook (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Crossing the Farther Shore: Dinh Q. Le, April - August 2014: Research (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Crossing the Farther Shore: Dinh Q. Le, April - August 2014: Research notebook (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Crossing the Farther Shore: Dinh Q. Le, April - August 2014: Events (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Crossing the Farther Shore: Dinh Q. Le, April - August 2014: Financial (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Crossing the Farther Shore: Dinh Q. Le, April - August 2014: Press release (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Crossing the Farther Shore: Dinh Q. Le, April - August 2014: Press received (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Crossing the Farther Shore: Dinh Q. Le, April - August 2014: Guestbook (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Crossing the Farther Shore: Dinh Q. Le, April - August 2014: Guest comment cards (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Crossing the Farther Shore: Dinh Q. Le, April - August 2014: Snapshots (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Crossing the Farther Shore: Dinh Q. Le, April - August 2014: Graphics (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Crossing the Farther Shore: Dinh Q. Le, April - August 2014: Travel (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Crossing the Farther Shore: Dinh Q. Le, April - August 2014: Words and Art event notebook (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Crossing the Farther Shore: Dinh Q. Le, April - August 2014: Video space, group exhibition, "In Transit" (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - New Installation: Yusuke Asai, Oct - Nov 2014: Research (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - New Installation: Yusuke Asai, Oct - Nov 2014: Installation (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - New Installation: Yusuke Asai, Oct - Nov 2014: Graphics (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - New Installation: Yusuke Asai, Oct - Nov 2014: Travel (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - New Installation: Yusuke Asai, Oct - Nov 2014: Soil samples labeled by source location (Box 42, Folder 47-49)
  - New Installation: Yusuke Asai, Oct - Nov 2014: Words and Art event notebook (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - Intersections: Anila Quayyum Agha, Dept. - Dec. 2015: press received (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Shotgun: Atelier Bow-Wow, Jan. - March, 2015: graphics and press received (Box 42, Folder 52)
  - Shotgun: Atelier Bow-Wow, Jan. - March, 2015: Words and Art event notebook (Box 42, Folder 53)
  - Unbounded: Ben Butler, June - August 2015, press received (Box 42, Folder 54)
  - Unbounded: Ben Butler, June - August 2015, Words and Art event notebook (Box 42, Folder 55)
  - Cubicle: Jonathan Schipper, Oct - Dec 2016, graphics (Box 42, Folder 56)
  - Glossy and Flat Black Squares: Sol LeWitt, Feb - May 2017, graphics and installation (Box 42, Folder 57)
  - Glossy and Flat Black Squares: Sol LeWitt, Feb - May 2017, guestbook (Box 42, Folder 58)
  - Glossy and Flat Black Squares: Sol LeWitt, Feb - May 2017, t-shirt (Box 42, Folder 59)
  - Gallery attendance notes, 2011-2016 (Box 42, Folder 60)
- Series VII: Financial records (restricted), 1991-2017; ser7
  Conditions Governing Access
  Financial records are restricted due to proivacy concerns and will be opened in 2037. Questions may be directed to the Director of the Woodson Research Center, woodson@rice.edu.
  - Subseries: FY 1991
    - Exhibition support (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Subseries: FY 1993
    - Fund: Friends (Box 43, Folder 2-3)
  - Subseries: 1994
    - Fund: Chillman (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Fund: Membership (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Subseries: FY 1995
    - Proof of 501(c)3 Status (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Fund: Chillman memorial (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Fund: deKuffner (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Fund: General expenses (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Fund: Kilgore (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Fund: Sewall (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Fund: Speakers (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Grants: Granting organizations (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Subseries: FY 1996
    - Fund: General expenses (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Funds: General funds (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Grants: General (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Grants: Texas Commission on the Arts (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Funds: Patrons (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Subseries: FY 1997
    - Funds: Chillman, Speakers, General (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Fund: DeKuffner (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Fund: Membership (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Fund: Sewall fund/ gallery fundraiser (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Exhibition finances: Exhibition support (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Grants: CACHH (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Grants: Granting organizations (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Subseries: FY 1998
    - Funding: Budget planning (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Funding: Museum District Day (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Funding: Patrons (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Funding: Special events (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Exhibit finances: Charles Howard (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Exhibit finances: Kusama (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Exhibit finances: Student show (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Grants: Granting organizations (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Subseries: FY 1999
    - Fund: Budget (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Fund: Budget overview (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Fund: Membership and patron (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Fund: Sewall (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Fund: Sponsors (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Exhibition finances: Nicole Eisenman (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Exhibition finances: Stephen Keene (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Subseries: FY 1999-2001
    - Fund: Brown foundation (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Subseries: FY 2000
    - Fund: Budget (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Fund: CACHH TCA (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Fund: Patrons (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Fund: Priorities (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Fund: revenues and expenses (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Funds: Sewall, De Kuffner, Kilgore (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Exhibition finances: Annual student show Check it Out (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Exhibition finances: Barry McGee (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Exhibition finances: Clubs of Bmako (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Exhibition finances: Kasten Haus, 2000-09-21-2000-10-29 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Exhibition finances: Shout outs (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Exhibition finances: Superthrive Stephen Henclee (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Grants: granting organizations (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Subseries: FY 2001
    - Fund: Annual Report (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Fund: Budget overview (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Fund: Budget request documents for dean (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Fund: financial budget worksheet (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Fund: Patron (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Fund: Sewall (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Fund: Sewall endowment (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Fund: Sponsors (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Fund: Sudler prize (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Exhibition finances: Celeste Boursler- Mougenot untitled, series #2 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Fund: DeKuffner (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Exhibition finances: Karim Rashid: Pleasurscape (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Fund: Kilgore (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Exhibition finances: Martha Burgess (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Exhibition finances:Summer Window James Cullinane: pastor and collux (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Fund: TCA thru CACHH (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Exhibition finances: Winter / Horbeit Crate House (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Grants: granting organizations (Box 45, Folder 14-15)
  - Subseries: FY 2002
    - Fund: Annual report (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Fund: DeKuffner (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Fund: Membership (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Fund: Sewall (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Exhibition finances: Adriana Arenas Ilian the Precious stone and gold factory (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Exhibition fiances: All That: Annual Rice student art show (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Exhibition finances: Jennifer Steinkamp - One saw, the other saw (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Exhibition fiances: Lee Mingwei The Tourist project (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Exhibition fiances: Liga pang IKASU (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Grants: TCA thru CACHH (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Subseries: FY 2003
    - Fund: Annual report (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - Fund: Membership (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - Fund: Sewall fund (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - Fund: Sewall endowment (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Fund: Sudler Prize (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Exhibition finances: Ester Partegas: Samesation (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Exhibition finances: Exit - 40th Annual Rice Student Art Show (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Exhibition finances: Phoebe Washburn: True, False, and slightly better (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Exhibition finances: Shigeruban: Bamboo Roof (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Subseries: FY 2004
    - Fund: Annual report (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Fund: Brown Foundation (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Fund: DeKuffner (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Fund: Membership (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Fund: Patron (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Fund: Sewall (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Exhibition finances: Ackroyd /Harvey: Green brick, green back (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Exhibition finances: Bercowetz / Bua - The Re-creation of Fort Discomfort (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Exhibition finances: Tara Donovan: Haze (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Exhibition finances: Under the Radar - 41st Annual Rice Student Art Show (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Subseries: FY 2004-2005
    - Exhibition finances: Summer window I Alyson Shotz: The Shape of Space (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Subseries: FY 2005
    - Fund: Brown Foundation (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Fund: Catalogue endowment (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Fund: DeKuffner (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Fund: Membership (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Fund: Patron (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Fund: Sewall (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Exhibition finances: Allen Ruppersberg - The Singing Posters (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Exhibition finances: Jacob Hashimoto: Superabundant Atmosphere (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Exhibition finances: Jessica Stockholder: Sam Ran over Sand or Sand Ran over Sam (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Exhibition finances: 42nd annual Rice student art show (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Subseries: FY 2006
    - Fund: DeKuffner (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Fund: Membership (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Fund: Patron (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Fund: Sewall (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Exhibition finances:David Ellis: Conversation (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Exhibition finances: Diane Landry: Flying School and Mandela Naya (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Exhibition finances: Lisa Hoke: Light My Fire (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Exhibition finances: Shine - 43rd Annual Rice Student Art Show (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Exhibition finances: White Webb: Eminent Domain (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Grant: Brown Foundation (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Subseries: FY 2007
    - Fund: Brown Foundation: Sarofim (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Fund: Brown Foundation: Wilson (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Fund: Catalogue endowment (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Fund: DeKuffner (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Fund: Membership (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Fund: Patron (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Fund: Sewall (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Exhibition finances: Art for Profit: Annual Rice Student Art Show (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Exhibition finances: Ball / Nogues: Rip Curl Canyon (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Exhibition finances: John Cerney: Big Landscape, Big West (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Exhibition finances: Judy Pfaff... all of the above (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Exhibition finances: Mike Stilkey: When the animals rebel (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Subseries: FY 2008
    - Fund: Brown foundation: Sarofim (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Fund: Brown foundation: Wilson (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Fund: DeKuffner (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Fund: Membership (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Fund: Sewall (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Exhibition finances: Charlie Roberts: Mambo Jambo (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Exhibition finances: Mark Fox: Dust (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Exhibition finances: Launch - Annual Rice Student Art Show (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Exhibition finances: Kristen Hassenfeld: Dans la Lune (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Subseries: FY 2009
    - Exhibition finances: DeKuffner (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Exhibition finances: Kilgore (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Fund: Membership (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Fund: Patrons (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Fund: Sewall (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Exhibition finances: Aurora Robson: The Great Indoors (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Exhibition finances: Henrique Oliveira: Tapumes (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Exhibition finances: Michael Salter: Too Much (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Exhibition finances: Paul Villinski: Emergency Response Studio (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Subseries: FY 2010
    - Fund: Brown Foundation: Sarofim (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Fund: Brown Foundation / Wilson (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Funds: Kilgore, Sewall, Sudler, Nightingale Code, Catalogue Endownment (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Fund: Membership (Box 48, Folder 22-23)
    - Fund: Patrons (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Fund: Save the Gallery (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Fund: Sewall (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Budget annual expenses FY 1994-2010 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Exhibit finances: Andrea Dezso (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Exhibit finances: El Anatsui / Gli (Wall) (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Exhibit finances: Sarah Oppenheimer D-17 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Exhibit finances: Wayne White (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Subseries: FY 2011
    - Fund: Brown Foundation (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Fund: Catalogue Endownment (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Fund: Membership (Box 49, Folder 11-12)
    - Fund: Patrons (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Fund: Sewall (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Exhibit finances: Ana Serrano, Salon of Beauty (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Exhibit finances: Joel Shapiro - New Installation (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Exhibit finances: Mary Temple - NW Corner SW Light (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Exhibit finances: Sarah Oppenheimer (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Exhibit finances: Summer Window (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Subseries: FY 2012
    - Fund: Brown Foundation (also including FY 2013) (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Fund: Membership (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Funds: Patron (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Funds: Sewall (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Funds: Sudler, Sewall, Kilgore, deKuffner, Catalogue Endowment (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Exhibit finances: Cave of the Forgotten Dreams (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Exhibit finances: Gunilla Klingberg (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Exhibit finances: Mary Temple (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Exhibit finances: Onishi Yasuaki (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Exhibit finances: Soo Sunny Park (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Exhibit finances: Steve Keene (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Exhibit finances: Tradition Redefined (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Subseries: FY 2013
    - Fund: Bucher Residency Gift Fund (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Fund: Patrons / Membership (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Exhibit finances: El Ultimo Grito (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Exhibit finances: Texas Contemporary Art Fair (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Subseries: FY 2014
    - Fund: Brown Foundation (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Fund: Patrons / Members (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Exhibit finances: Andrew Piscayne (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Exhibit finances: Cubicle (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Exhibit finances: Dinh Q. Le (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Subseries: FY 2015
    - Fund: Patrons / Membership (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Exhibit finances: Atelier Bow-Wow (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Exhibit finances: Ben Butler (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Exhibit finances: Texas Contemporary Art Fair (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Exhibit finances: Yusuke Asai (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Subseries: FY 2016
    - Fund: Patrons / Members (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Exhibition finances: Anila Agha (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Exhibition finances: Summer Window (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Exhibition finances: Thorsten Brinkman (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Subseries: FY 2017
    - Fund: Donations (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Catalogue shipping project (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - Exhibition finances: Jonathan Schipper (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - Exhibition finances: Yusuke Asai (Box 50, Folder 31)
- Series VIII: Museum Studies course
  - Syllabi, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Anthropology vs. Art (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Art Handling (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Basics (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Bibliographies (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Bill's Syllabus (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Careers (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Censorship (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Collecting (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Cultural Patrimony (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Deaccessioning (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Education (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Education/Labels (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Museums as Entertainment (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Ethics (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Museum History (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Museum as Muse (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Inside the White Cube (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Installation and Display (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Internships (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Nazi Plunder (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Native American Issues (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Orphaned Collections (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Samples/Mission Statements (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Samples/Press Releases (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Trustees (Box 51, Folder 26)
- Series IX: Press, outreach and programming notebooks
  - Press/Programming for Rice Student Shows, 1995-1998 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Press, 2005-2006 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Email Blasts, 2008-2011 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Press, 2009 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Press Bibliography, Fall 2009 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Press: Dateline Rice, 2009-2010 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - Press Received, 2010 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - Administrative and Outreach overview, 2011-2012 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Press: Dateline Rice, 2010-2011 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - Michael de Feo: Crosstown Traffic About the Artist, 2016 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - Programming: Mary Temple (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - Programming: Sarah Oppenheimer (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Programming: Ana Serrano, 2012 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Exhibit Attendance Tallies, 1991-2001 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Exhibit Attendance Guestbook, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Series X: Awards
  - Awards for Rice Art Gallery (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Award letters for Bill Camfield CAA, 1992-1995 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Series XI: Exhibition photography addendum
  - Exhibit images (35 mm slide format), 1981-1995 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Exhibit images (35 mm slide format), 1981-1986 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Exhibit images (compact disc format, content saved on nearline server as UA0066aip_002 through UA0066aip_067), 2000-2005 (Box 52, Folder -)
- Series XII: Digital content from compact discs
  - Various RAG documents (Folder "2000-2001")
  - Kaustenhaus exhibit documents (Folder "2000-2001")
  - Martha Burgess, Manly on the Plaid (Folder "2000-2001")
  - Various correspondence and promotional material (Folder "2000-2001")
  - Exhibit photos (Folder "2001-2002")
  - Exhibit photos (Folder "2001-2002")